Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5305
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Beaunit Corp. vs. Local 2207, UTWA, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  [Folder entitled 6(A-C)]#72-6 Complaints, Arbitrator's Notes, Summary Statement of Each Grievance, Contracts - Dispute Settlement (Dated 8/23/71 - 3/27/72)
- City of New York (Off-Track Betting Corp.) vs. District Council #37, AFSCME, 3/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  #72-7 Correspondence - Arbitrator Removed Himself from Case
- Erstein Oil & Utilities, Inc.vs. Local 355, Amalgamated, 3/6/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  #72-9 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Correspondence - Schedules of Works, Past Practice, Overtime
- Pictorial Power Co. vs. Local 1-P, NYLPEU 4/17/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  #72-10 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Reduction in Pay
- Poughkeepsie Iron & Metal Co. vs. local 455, IABSOIW, 4/10/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  #72-11 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Vacation Pay
- Queensboro Public Library vs. Local 1321, District Council 37, AFSCME, 5/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  #72-12 Mediator's Notes, Contract Proposals, Minutes of Negotiation Meetings, Portions of Old Contract, Modified Contract, Newspaper Clipping, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- Simmons Co. vs. Local 420, Simmons Elizabeth Employees Union, 3/23/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  #72-13 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. Local 2, UFT, 11/29/73, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  #72-14 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Suspension, Reinstatement, Back Pay
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. J.L. Calleja (Box 40, Folder 14)
  #72-15 Grievance Report, Correspondence - Furloughed, Bumping
- DeLaval Separator Co. vs. Lodge 1598, IAM, 5/1/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  [Folder entitled 1(A-B)]#72-16 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, U.S. Code of Intoxicating Liquors, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Drinking & Intoxication, Rehabilitation
- City of New York vs. District Council #37, AFSCME, 5/19/72 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  #72-17 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Welfare Funds
- Mobil Oil Corp. vs. OCAWIU, 10/10/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  #72-19 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Richardson Co. vs. Local 913, RWCLPWA, 5/18/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  [Folder entitled 4(A-C)] #72-20 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Negligence & Carelessness, Burden of Proof
- Tri-State Iron Works, Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 8/16/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  #72-21 Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Settled During Hearing
- Helena Rubenstein, Inc. vs. Local 8-149, OCAWU, 3/9/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  #72-22 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- F.W. Woolworth Co. vs. Local 804, IBT, 3/30/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  #72-23 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee E, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Fights & Altercation
- City of New York (X-Ray Technicians) vs. Local 237, IBT, 5/18/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  #72-24 Mediator's Notes, Correspondence - Salary Dispute
- R.H. Macy & Co vs. Local 1-S, RWDSU (Box 41, Folder 9)
  #72-25 Correspondence - Hearing Postponed due to Strike
- New York Seven-Up Bottling Co. vs. Local 445, IBT (Box 41, Folder 10)
  #72-26 Correspondence - Hearing Postponed
- Kuritzky's Diary, Inc. vs. Local 338, IBT, 4/26/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  [Folder entitled 11(A--B)] #72-27 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Past Arbitration Award, Employer Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Improper Job Attitude
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. Mrs. Tellie Butler (Box 41, Folder 12)
  #72-28 Correspondence - Hearing Postponed
- Pakulas Inc. vs. Local 1111, RCIA, 5/30/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  #72-30 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Mutually Settled During Hearing
- Beach Nut Inc. vs. Local 697, BCW, 5/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  #72-32 Correspondence - Change of Job Content
- Carter Rubber Co. vs. Local 149, BSWU, 6/15/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  [Folder entitled 15(A-B)] #72-33 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Leaving Work Area Without Permission, Improper Personal Conduct
- Electronic Reproduction Service vs. Dist. 65, RWDSU (Box 41, Folder 16)
  #72-34 Correspondence - Hearing Postponed - Case Awaiting Court Hearing
- Sunshine Biscuits, Inc. vs. Local 478, IBT, 5/24/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  #72-35 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Correspondence Seniority, Lay-off
- Ideal Roller, W.R. Grace & Co. vs. Local 810, IBT 5/23/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  #72-36 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Employer Exhibits, Map of Building, Correspondence - Reporting Pay
- Town of Rye vs. Local 456, IBT, 5/9/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  #72-37 Mediator's Notes, Contract Proposals, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation, Recommendation Fact-Finding
- Town of Mt. Pleasant vs. Local 456, IBT, 8/23/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  Mediator's Notes, Contract Proposals, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation, Recommendation: Fact-Finding
- Johns-Manville Products Corp. vs. Local 800, UPP (Box 41, Folder 21)
  #72-39 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- The New York Times Co. vs. Local 1-P, NYLPEU, 5/9/72, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  #72-40 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Vacations, Past Practice
- Armstrong Cork Co. (Braintree, Mass.) vs. Local 22619, URCLPWA, 6/23/72, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  [Folder entitled 1(A-D)] #72-41 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Absences, Tardiness
- General Envelope Co. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 8/27/72, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  #72-42 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Holiday Pay, Rates of Pay
- Washington Turbine International vs. Local 1580, IAM, 7/24/72, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  #72-43 Correspondence - Arbitration Canceled, Attempting Mediation
- Southworth Machine Co. vs. Lodge 895, IAM, 6/8/72, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  #72-44 Correspondence - Mutually Settled By Parties
- City of New York vs. Licensed Practical Nurses of New York Inc., 10/17/72, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  [Folder entitled 5(A-D)] #72-45 Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, Employer Exhibits
- Glen Cove City School District vs. Glen Cove Teachers Association, 6/19, 9/30/72, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  [Folder entitled 6(A-E)] #72-46 Decisions, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Brief, Employee Affirmation, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Miscellaneous Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations (See Box 42A for Hearing Transcripts)
- City of New York vs. The Podiatry Society of State of New York, 9/25/72, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  [Folder entitled 7(A-F)] #72-47 Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Miscellaneous Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- City of New York vs. Licensed Practical Nurses of New York, Inc. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  [Box entitled 42A while Folder is titled 1(A-C)] #72-45 Hearing Transcripts (See Box 42-5 for full case material)
- Bayview Nursing Center vs. Local 1115, NHHEU, 7/6/72, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  #72-48 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- City of New York vs. Local 237, IBT, 12/19/72 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  [Folder entitled 2(A-B)] #72-49 Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, Hearing transcript, Exhibit, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- City of New York (Queens Borough Public Library) vs. Local 1321, District Council 37, AFSCME, 7/13/72, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  #72-50 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Shift Scheduling
- Hess Oil and Chemical Co. vs. Local 22026, Federal Labor Union, 10/27/72, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  #72-51 Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Pacific & Southern Co., Inc. vs. Local 1212 IBEW, 7/19/72 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  #72-52 Decisions Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Old Contract Correspondence - Shift Scheduling, Bargaining Unit Worker
- New York City Board of Education vs. UFT, 6/26/72, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  #72-53 Correspondence - Mutually Settled By Parties
- Edgemont Union Free School District #6 vs. Edgemont Teachers Associations, 6/21/72, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  [Folder entitled 7(A-D)] #72-54 Fact-Finder's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- White Plains City School District vs. White Plain Teachers Association 8/23/72, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  [Folder entitled 8(A-E)] #72-55 Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Report, Employee Rebuttal Brief, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation